

ABOUT ME

I'm a creative and driven engineering student with a big interest in technology and design. My goal is to become an expert in the interaction between human and machine, as well as to create user-friendly technology that is easy and fun to use.

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

Winner Nasa Space Apps Challenge 2022

Winner of Good Tech Hack 2021

Great Leaders certificate

Skills in:

- Java, C, Matlab, HTML, CSS, React, Javascript, SQL, Java
- Figma, Axure
- Adobe Photoshop och Illustrator

CONTACT ME

Mobile: 070-220 62 18

E-mail: emma.rosenlind@gmail.com Portfolio: www.erosenlind.com LinkedIn: @emmarosenlind

Address: Lokevägen 14 85741 Sundsvall

EMMA ROSENLIND

Master of Science Engineering student

EDUCATION

Umeå University

M.Sc Engineering within Interaction Technology and Design 2019 - 2024*

Korea University

Engineering semester abroad Fall 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

System Developer /Accessibility designer

ITS (Umeå University) | June 2023 - August 2023

 Accessibility improvement for the administration system used by Sweden's universities

UX/UI designer

We Know It | May 2021 - May 2023

- Consultant to several different types of clients
- Delivered prototypes, user flows, graphic material, user tests, etc.
- Responsible for internal design matters and recruitment

UX summer intern

Osynlig | June 2022 - August 2022

B2B salesman

Mittmedia (Bonnier News) | April 2019 - Augusti 2019

VOLUNTEERING

Board Member

DataTjej | May 2022 - May 2023

• IT och website manager

PR and Mentor Manager

Pepp | May 2022 - May 2023

Volleyball Coach

Stenstadens VBK | 2017 - 2019